AARON AGOSTO

Software Engineer - Open to Relocation - Portfolio

FTL, FL | (954)-701-5274 | aaronagostodev@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/aaronagosto/ | github.com/AaronMAgosto

Programming Languages: JavaScript | HTML | CSS | TypeScript

Technologies: React / React Native | AWS | Express | Git/Bash | Node.js | MongoDB | Firebase | Postman |

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software engineer completing over 700+ hours of solid foundations in software development principles and technologies. Demonstrated project management skills, effectively leading teams to complete projects valued over \$2.0 million. Engineering expertise lies in the FERN/MERN techstack.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Boca Code, Software Engineering Career Course - May 2023

Boca Raton, FL

Broward College, Associate in Science - Jul 2019 - Jul 2020

Davie, FL

Certifications: Figma for UX Design (2023) | UX for Web Design (2023)

PROJECTS

Honey Hole - React Web-Based App LIVE | REPO

2023

- Developed a **React** web-based project aimed at assisting South Florida residents in discovering ideal fishing spots.
- Utilized MongoDB as the database and implemented Express, Node.js, and JavaScript for functionality.
 Implemented full CRUD operations and designed a RESTful API.
- Employed multiple components to enhance the overall functionality and user interface of the application.

Boca Code Hackathon - React Web-Based App LIVE

2023

 Collaborated in a hackathon to revamp the candidates section of a website, incorporating a Q&A section, project links, and an introduction feature. Implemented these enhancements to improve user engagement and provide comprehensive information about the candidates.

Lunch Spot - React Native Mobile App REPO

2023

- Developed a React Native mobile app for finding local restaurants, integrating API calls and Google reviews.
- Implemented stack and swipe navigation and a user friendly interface to optimize performance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX/UI MERN Developer Internship

Boca Raton, FL

Boca Code

June 2023 – Present

- UX/UI focused. Creating a portfolio with graphic novels for anime using Generative AI images and building with Tailwind CSS, Javascript, and Next JS.
- Collaborating in an Agile/Scrum methodology with weekly stand-up meetings with a team of 10+ engineers.
- Translating Figma mockups into interactive and responsive web applications, ensuring seamless user experience.

Prestige Electric

Parkland, FL

Field Electrician/Technician

June 2022 – Mar 2023

- Leading the lighting team of 4+ electricians to wire and install high-tech stair lighting and entertainment systems at renowned nightclubs like **DAER** at the **Guitar Hotel**. Project worth \$50,000 and completed within budget.
- Oversaw installation of energy-efficient LED lighting systems in 40+ houses with a team of four electricians per project, achieving completion within 8 months and generating \$200,000 in revenue for the business.
- Effectively communicated with clients to resolve conflicts and collect payments for completed projects, resulting in high levels of customer satisfaction and repeat business.

International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers

Palm Beach County, FL

Field Electrician/Technician

June 2021 – June 2022

- Collaborated with my team of **7+** and contributed to multi-million dollar projects by installing custom-built lighting fixtures ranging between \$10,000 and \$80,000
- Managed and led a team of electricians on a series of underground electrical projects for over 25+ homes, installing over 300+ fixtures.